[Applause]
first of all thank you very much for
coming here and being part of this
conference I think that there are more
than 200 people in this hotel interested
in react native this week which is
exciting
so before we start let me tell you why
we decided to organize this conference
in first place react native has been out
there in a while for more than two years
now it's not longer at soy or yet
another fancy framework that can just
disappear the day after it's now a
serious platform that can have real
impact on the progress building and it
also changes the way we think about
mobile development in general right the
promise of platform agnostic JavaScript
that can run on many platforms at once
is attracting many developers from
different backgrounds starting from
project management and ending up with
native mobile development and so since
they all approach react native and
mobile development from a different
perspective the problems they are facing
are different I've read once on the
internet that attending conferences
doesn't make any sense they are
expensive the talks are recorded that
I'm being uploaded to the Internet so
what's the point right if all you can
get is free materials on YouTube well
for me it's us the community we don't
attend conferences just to listen to the
talks that you will be hearing after my
after my talk we attend these
conferences to talk with each other to
share our experience and learn how we
can write better apps together and
that's the reason and that's the real
reason why events like this exists you
know I'm also super excited about the
lineup that we have I believe that next
two days will change the way you think
about mobile development with react
native we have carefully selected 20
speakers each using react native in a
different way to sure that your
experience these challenges they are
facing on daily basis you will hear
everything here in order to get
productive react native starting from
how to plan the app in general ending up
with how to use condoms deployment
services in
to deploy your app right away to your
users since there is no dedicated time
for questions after each talk I
encourage you to remember your questions
and find speakers during coffee breaks
and just ask them there are a few
companies that I wanted to mention here
first of all thank you very much
formidable array index for coming here
and doing workshops on free as you know
the workshops that we decided to do this
year were slightly different than our
competitors regularly do other
conferences let's say we wanted to make
a university university that everyone
can attend and so we made it in a way
that we try to talk to as many people
and as many companies as possible and
try to convince them that the nonprofit
idea of a workshop is the best thing
that can happen for the community also
thank you very much in fin red for
partnering with us sharing your Twitter
sharing your customers user base to help
us kickstart the idea of react native
you and get very very first followers so
thank you very much for this without you
we wouldn't be here and you know now may
be a question did you already have
coffee today or planning to have yeah so
you can now go to native base repo give
them a star because today we are having
coffee thanks to them thank you and of
course this entire event wouldn't be
wouldn't happen if it wasn't for Cole
stack
now Cole stack is a company I co-founded
with Anna she's here on she's here in
the audience as well
we are JavaScript experts focused on the
reactive react native in particular we
have a lot of activity in the open
source and in the community if you are
following react native you probably seen
us doing releases from science a time or
you heard about Hall which is a
alternative to react native package or
that we doing and we are based here in
verse 12 so if this sounds like a geek
for you let us know we will be happy to
tell you more how how does it feel to
work at Cole Stagg and how you can apply
feel free to ask anyone from coal stock
about details we are wearing our
custom-made sweet work clothes military
style so we are kind of easy to locate
today and finally I just wanted to give
you a quick reminder about our code of
conduct that you can read in detail at
code of conduct comm since we kind of
put the link in the footer and I'm
pretty sure that some of you missed it
I'm just going to read it quick version
now and then we can start our conference
is dedicated to providing a harassment
free conference experience for everyone
regardless of gender gender identity and
expression age sexual orientation
disability physical appearance body size
race religion or lack thereof or
technology choices we do not tolerate
harassment of conference participants in
any form sexual language and imagery is
not appropriate for any conference venue
including talks workshops parties
Twitter and other online media
conference participants violating these
rules may be sanctioned or expelled from
the conference with other we found at
the discretion of the conference
organizers so I just wanted to remind
you that we are here together as a
community to have a great time and to
learn from each other about reactive so
let's make this time perfect for each
other
in case you experience any of this or
witness any of these activities please
report immediately to staff members or
to CoStar employees wearing our shooter
style so that's it for now I'm going to
come when I unplug my laptop the first
speaker will come up here and let the
party begin thank you very much and
enjoy the next two days
[Applause]